Why do you not kill me?
Let me ask you this, as well: why did
you not fight with the intent to kill?
What?
The other Insects that came
from the Underworld Gate
are desperate to take over this world.
Yes, that is our most ardent wish.
You are hesitant.
Could it be that you're
opposed to that goal?
The Underworld is impoverished.
We have no future unless we
take over the mortal world.
But I do not understand it.
Hey, Gran...
Yeah.
I don't dislike oddballs like you.
What do you say to coming with us?
Go... with you?
Me? An Insect?
Is that so strange?
We need to leave from here on
a long journey to the west.
So we'd like to have some
allies we can trust.
What is your name?
I have no name.
Oh? Then I'll give you one.
Right!
From now on, your name is Razul.
Whoa... That took a lot out of me.
I'm Maria, and this is...
Gran.
Glad to know you, Razul.
Gran... Maria...
That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime
Season 4
Episode 95: Granville's Hope
I'm saving Chloe and Hinata's souls.
If I intervene with their souls
while they sleep inside Chronoa
and speak to them through Thought
Communication, maybe I can wake them.
But... how?
What are my odds of success?
There is a way to further solidify
your plan's chance of success.
I wanted to relay that to you.
And what is it?
Right, if you take the form of your
spiritual body while maintaining contact
between your physical bodies,
you can enter the other being's body.
Then, if your astral
bodies come into contact,
you can directly intervene
with the other being's soul.
That sounds like I'd risk getting stuck in
there and never being able to come back...
Raphael-sensei, can I not just talk
to them with Thought Communication?
Answer.
The suggestion from the individual
named Diablo is more likely to succeed.
However, the danger level
is also incomparably higher.
Got it.
Thanks, Diablo.
Let me just say one thing, though.
Yes? What is it?
You seriously overestimate me.
You are being too modest.
Well, I wish you luck, Great Rimuru.
I'm not being modest.
Anyway, how can I get
Chronoa to calm down?
I can't make contact with that.
Why not try using the
magic-suppressing mask?
Charys?!
Crap! I said that out loud!
Wait, so you figured out
what I was thinking, too?
That mask was powerful
enough to keep me sealed.
I feel that it may also
help to quiet her spirit.
I get it.
Maybe the mask Chloe inherited
from Shizu-san can...
Hang on. Where is that mask now, anyway?
If it came back to the past with Chloe,
would it end up back with Shizu-san again?
So where did that mask come
from in the first place, then?
No, I can think about that later.
Raphael-sensei,
can you reproduce that mask?
Answer.
Would you like to create a replica
of the magic-suppressing mask?
Yes.
Help me, Shizu-san.
Now I just need to wait for them
to create an opening for me.
Everyone, get behind me!
I'm a dungeon boss, too—
You stay here!
Where did Chlo-chi go?
For real! Just because she's
strong is no reason to...
I wish we could go look for her...
What now?!
You still refuse to admit defeat?
Then I will end it here.
I will defeat you and join Gran.
You think I'm going to let you?
Death Storm!
Some sort of force field?
None of my magic has been
reaching him at all.
The same goes for Shion's attacks.
Is that exoskeleton tougher
than steel or what?
What incredible force...
I can't even escape it when
I evade using Ultra Instinct.
So this is what an Insect in
its final form is capable of...
I heard about Maribel.
You are ready to make
your final wager, yes?
Yes.
She reminded me of Maria a bit.
Agreed.
With her gone, there is no one
else worthy of being my successor.
Even I cannot live forever.
To think that Gran's hope has been lost,
after he fought back against
hardship after hardship
and was so close to achieving
his dream of so many years...
Gran, you will make your
wish come true, yes?
My path is forever by your side,
no matter where that may lead me.
As I told you, you are
the only one I trust.
You can count on me, Gran.
I will not allow anyone to get in
the way of your—no, our dream.
Ranga, take a break for a while.
I've got Ultraspeed Regeneration.
Don't be ridiculous! That thing is strong!
We've been fighting him
together, and look at us!
It's all right.
I think I'm figuring him out.
Save your strength until
I give you the signal.
Understood.
Your resolve is admirable.
I'll strip you of that confidence!
Oh?
My Wicked Oni skill, Oni Berserker.
Oni Berserker
The burden of boosting my strength,
stamina, and spirit is immense.
I need to finish this
before I lose my sanity!
I can't go down now.
If I die now, our chances of winning
this battle will drop severely.
Even if I can't win, I can buy time.
I need to keep him here!
All that matters is that I stay alive.
That said, I have no
intention of giving up!
I will win and earn Great Rimuru's praise!
Shion?
Mere child's play!
Shion's technique has clearly
increased since this battle began.
She relied solely on her
strength before, but now...
I'm not done!
I've still got much more in me!
My unique skill, Master Chef.
No matter how tough he is,
its Certain Outcome can bend
the rules until he breaks!
I have one goal:
to destroy his exoskeleton!
Even after all this...
Shion, I'll join you!
No, not yet!
Foolish.
Shion!
Admit defeat.
Are you ready to submit to me now?
Don't make me laugh.
What?
Submit to you?
I aspire to reach even greater heights.
What are you...
You are one clueless bug.
I'm saying that I will surpass you!
Your attacks simply are
not enough to affect me.
Admit that you are weak.
And the weak can accomplish nothing.
Yes, it's true. You're right.
I am weak.
As an Ogre, I always
believed might made right.
Weak ones die.
Among monsters, that's to be expected.
That's why
Great Rimuru's rule of never looking down
on other races resonated with me.
But when I died, I felt the fear
of being killed for the first time.
And then Great Rimuru saved me.
The relief I felt then...
Listen, Shion. What's important is...
...knowing where your soul is.
Great Rimuru said that the worth of your
soul is determined by how you live.
That whether you're strong
or weak means nothing.
So behold how I choose to live!
It's so pathetic.
There were times when I felt uncertain
because I am inferior to Diablo.
I thought Great Rimuru might toss me
out someday because I lacked strength.
That is what weakness is to me!
What use is there in envying others?
It is myself I should be focusing on!
I must overcome myself!
Confirmed.
The individual named Shion's
intrinsic skill Oni Berserker
Oni Berserker
has evolved into the unique
skill Divine Berserker.
Divine Berserker
Here I come!
This is futile.
My exoskeleton cannot be—
Shut up!
I'm going to teach you something:
the goddess of victory smiles upon the
one who doesn't give up until the end!
Here I come!
Divine Release!
The pressure is immense...
but it's nothing to me!
Ranga!
Understood!
Insolence!
Chaotic Fate!
Now!
I'm on it!
Just wait, Chloe, Hinata!
I swear I'm going to save your souls!
I am sorry, Gran.
It seems this is the end for me.
I will die first.
We shall meet again at
the promised location...
Shion!
Ranga, we still have to—
The world is constantly
trampling upon my wish.
Even now, I have lost yet another friend.
You mean Razul?
So all I need to do now
is destroy this world.
Don't be ridiculous!
If you want to despair, do it on your own!
Despair?
Why, not at all.
In this very moment,
my heart has been filled
to the brim with hope.
Now is the time to fulfill my promise
to my friends and loved ones.
Confirmed. Conditions met.
Indomitable
The individual named Granville
Rozzo's skill Indomitable
Sariel
has evolved into the
ultimate skill Sariel.
Hope?
Yes. My preparations are complete.
You must have done it, Rimuru.
All I can do now is believe in you.
Lady Luminus, let us at last cut our
ties and settle this once and for all.
Indeed. I will see for myself
just how prepared you are.
And do not worry.
I will be certain to kill you.
My Asmodeus and Gran's Sariel...
It is likely they both
command life and death.
When the conditions are the
same, the stronger will wins.
This will be over in an instant.
Memory End Requiem!
Memory End Requiem
Fortitude!
Well done, Lady Luminus...
Am I inside Chronoa's mental realm?
That's... what I want, right?
I managed to get in?
Where the heck am I
supposed to go, though?
Hey.
It's been a long time, Slime-san.
Rather... Satoru-san, right?
Shizu-san!
Oh, I get it. This is all a mentalscape.
Aw, cut it out. My name is Rimuru now.
I'm not throwing away my past,
but it's embarrassing being called that.
Well, shall we?
Huh?
She really is pretty.
You came to see her, didn't you?
Chronoa?!
Can she talk?
In the real world, she lost her
sense of self and went on a rampage.
Go on.
Right. We should try talking first.
Chronoa?
Are you... Rimuru?
Y-Yeah.
Is it really you?
Yeah. I'm definitely the real Rimuru-san.
Rimuru!
This isn't what I imagined...
I thought she'd be more antagonistic.
That said...
I like the idea of a cute girl
who'll hug a slime!
You accomplished so much.
I wish I could've met you, Hero.
Yeah.
She does seem more like Chloe.
I guess she really is
Chloe's grown-up form.
I'm curious why she went
on a rampage, though...
Um... Chronoa, was it?
Yeah. I'm Chronoa.
The "avatar of destruction"
that was sealed within Chloe,
and at the same time,
a sort of second personality.
I don't think I would've had such a sense
of self if Hinata hadn't named me, though.
I-I see.
I actually don't get it, but it sounds
like things are kinda complicated.
Listen, I came here looking
for Chloe and Hinata.
Could I see them?
That won't work.
Why not?
Chloe is lost in the Unlimited
Imprisonment deep inside me.
And Hinata...
Hinata is already dead.
What?
Next time, "The Hero Awakens."
The Hero Awakens